<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>business on Daniel Wagner</title>
    <link>https://danielwagner.at/categories/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in business on Daniel Wagner</description>
    <image>
      <title>Daniel Wagner</title>
      <url>https://danielwagner.at/img/logo.webp</url>
      <link>https://danielwagner.at/img/logo.webp</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.122.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:16:16 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://danielwagner.at/categories/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://danielwagner.at/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 15:29:13 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielwagner.at/page/about/</guid>
      <description>With over 15 years of experience in the IT industry, I have gained a diverse background through various roles held in different organizations, such as software engineer, project manager, and enterprise architect.
My focus is on designing software development and IT processes, applying agile methods, analyzing IT landscapes, planning software and integration architectures, for example for individual software or ERP solutions.
I have two degrees from the Vienna University of Technology in computer science and computer science management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offering</title>
      <link>https://danielwagner.at/page/offering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 22:14:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielwagner.at/page/offering/</guid>
      <description>Talks and Workshops Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of my recent and upcomming public talks and workshops
MAD Summit München 2024 , &amp;nbsp;June 10, 2024 OAuth 2.0 und OpenID Connect: Schlüssel zur sicheren Authentifizierung Munich, Germany BASTA! Frankfurt 2024 , &amp;nbsp;February 15, 2024 AuthNZ für APIs und Web-Apps mit IdentityServer Frankfurt/Main, Germany BASTA! Mainz 2023 , &amp;nbsp;September 25, 2023 OpenID Connection (fast) selbstgemacht mit IdenityServer Mainz, Germany ECR Tag 2023 , &amp;nbsp;September 14, 2023 Schnitten aus der Cloud – Wie das Wiener Traditionsunternehmen Manner den EDI-Nachrichtenaustausch mit Kunden, Logistikern und Lieferanten erfolgreich in die Cloud migriert hat Frankfurt, Germany MAD Summit München 2023 , &amp;nbsp;June 19, 2023 Standardbasierte Authentifzierung mit OAuth 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imprint &amp; Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://danielwagner.at/page/imprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 15:29:30 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielwagner.at/page/imprint/</guid>
      <description>Media proprietor/publisher of this website Structegra Digital Strategy e.U. Owner: DI Mag. Daniel Wagner
Bahnweg 3 Haus 1 3425 Langenlebarn Austria
Phone +43 677 61 62 61 12 E-Mail daniel@structegra.eu
Legal form: Sole proprietorship Place of business: Langenlebarn, Austria Commercial register number: 582479m Commercial Register Court: Regional Court St. Pölten VAT Reg. No: ATU78846108 GISA code: 34911747 and 37624729 D-U-N-S Number: 30-085-0574
Chamber membership: Austrian Federal Economic Chamber (WKÖ) Authority according to ECG (E-Commerce Act): Bezirkshauptmannschaft Tulln Applicable commercial or professional regulations: Gewerbeordnung 1994</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media and press</title>
      <link>https://danielwagner.at/page/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 07:38:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://danielwagner.at/page/media/</guid>
      <description>In media and press</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
